

PROFILE

Want to put your own image in the circle? It is easy! Select the image and do a right mouse click. Select "Fill" from the shortcut menu. Choose Picture... from the list. Navigate your computer to get the appropriate picture. Click okay to insert your selected image.

Once your image has been inserted, select it again. Go to the Picture Tools Format menu. Click on the down arrow below "Crop" and select "Fill" from the list. This will auto adjust your image to crop to the image. You can click and drag your image to place it appropriately.

CONTACT

PHONE: 812-319-8015

EMAIL:

jkohlscout@gmail.com

HOBBIES

Hobby #1

Hobby #2

Hobby #3

Hobby #4

JEREMY KOHLMAN

FRFF AGENT

EDUCATION

Indiana University - Bloomington

2009 - 2013

B.S. in Kinesiology

Major: Sports Marketing and Management

Minor: Business, Coaching

Indiana University - Bloomington

2016 - 2018

M.S. in Kinesiology

Focus: Athletic Administration and Sports Management

WORK EXPERIENCE

Royal United Mortgage - Loan Processor

2019-present

- Act as liaison between borrowers and financial institutions to assist qualified applicants acquire loans in a timely manner.
- Call and request documents for loan approval including appraisals, title commitments, tax certification, tax transcripts, credit information, and credit supplements.
- In 2020 and 2021, responsible for over 1,000 loan approvals for qualified applicants.

Big Red Liquors - Store Manager

2013-2019

- Oversee sales of \$1M in sales for the 1st time in location history.
- Lead merchandising and marketing of store products.

Indiana University Football - Graduate Assistant 2012–2018

- Evaluate film of high school athletes for coaches for further evaluation. Maintain the offensive and defensive recruiting boards.
- Keep track of all offers and commitments of top targets.
- Assist in the coordination and execution of all official and unofficial visits.

Kansas City Chiefs – Training Camp Intern

2011-2013

- Worked on various work teams that dealt with the public, customer relations, family interaction (players' families), security, sales, corporate sponsors, and fan experience.
- Set-up and tore down NFL training camp and escorted families to and from practice field while assisting with their needs ensuring NFL practice was fan-friendly and increased fan engagement and experience.
- Escorted VIPs around practice fields and ensured their safety during practice
- Top 3 in Kid's Club Registration sales in 2012 and 2013.